Contact

Toronto 1-647-702-6732 (Mobile) horaceheaven@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/horaceheaven (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Reinforcement Learning
Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Languages

English

Certifications

Certified Kubernetes Administrator Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist

AWS Certified Security - Specialty
AWS Certified Solutions Architect
AWS Databricks Platform Architect

Honors-Awards

Dean's Honor Roll

Dean's Honor Roll

The Odain Whittingham Aaward for Academic Excellence

Horace Heaven

Senior Solutions Architect at OpsGuru

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Summary

Certifications: Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist, Certified Kubernetes Application Developer, Certified Kubernetes Administrator & AWS Certified Security - Specialty

Specialties: Amazon Web Services (AWS), Containers (Kubernetes), Software Engineering, Artificial Intelligence (Machine Learning, Generative AI)

Insightful, pragmatic, and self-motivated professional who takes a genuine interest in delivering effective, efficient, and timely solutions. I operate with a strong sense of ownership, a 'can do' attitude, and a vision of what matters to make an organization successful.

Experience

OpsGuru

Senior Solutions Architect November 2021 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

As a AWS consulting partner, we're helping customers to meet their business goals, by taking full advantage of Amazon Web Services as their Cloud Computing, and Big Data Analytics platform.

At OpsGuru I'm working with customers to define and implement modern end-to-end solutions on AWS. Specialty projects: Containers (Kubernetes), Machine Learning (MLops), Big Data & Security.

Onica

Solutions Architect

August 2018 - November 2021 (3 years 4 months)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Led consulting projects and engineers, working with customers to define and implement modern end-to-end solutions on AWS. Specialty projects: Containers (Kubernetes), Machine Learning (MLops), Big Data & Security.

Page 1 of 2

TriNimbus

Solutions Architect

September 2017 - August 2018 (1 year)

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

Acquired by Onica

Specialty consulting projects: Containers (Kubernetes), Machine Learning, Big Data & Security.

Medullan

4 years 4 months

Software Engineer (Platform Development)

January 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 9 months)

Trinidad and Tobago

Led the architecture, implementation & deployment of Medullan's healthcare platform to AWS.

Designed & Implemented the necessary security controls to assist Medullan in achieving industry security compliance standards.

Developed & Architected scalable Front-end & Backend services for Medullan's healthcare platform.

Software Engineer (Consulting)

June 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 7 months)

Trinidad and Tobago

Designed & Developed Front-end, Backend and Mobile Solutions for large Health care industry clients.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Master of Science - MS, Computer Science · (2017 - 2020)

University of Technology, Jamaica

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science, First Class

Honours · (2009 - 2013)

Cornwall College

High School · (2004 - 2009)